findandtry.com 2013-05-28

# FindandTry: Privacy Policy

### FindandTry **Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason; each version will apply to information collected while it was in place. We Sun Social Media Inc., a Delaware corporation ("FINDANDTRY") will notify you of any material changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy on our Site. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Capitalized terms not otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy are defined in the FindAndTry.com Terms of Service.

By using our Site (www.FINDANDTRY.com) you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. "Processing" means using cookies on a computer or using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information, all of which activities will take place in the United States. If you reside outside the U.S. your personally identifiable information will be transferred to the U.S., and processed and stored there under U.S. privacy standards. By visiting our Site and providing information to us, you consent to such transfer to, and processing in, the US.

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or our use of your personally identifiable information, please contact us at [privacy@findandtry.com](mailto:privacy@findandtry.com).

  * ### Information Collection and Use

**Information Collected Upon Registration.** If you desire to have access to certain restricted sections of the Site or to order certain products from this Site, you will be required to become a registered user. As part of becoming a registered user or as part of ordering certain products from us as an unregistered user you will be required to submit certain personally identifiable information about yourself and others to FINDANDTRY. This happens in a number of instances, such as when you sign up for the Service. Personally identifiable information that we may collect in such instances may include your name, address, IP address, full user name, password, email address, time zone, telephone number, image/likeness and other information that you decide to provide to us, or that you decide to include in your public and private profile. In addition, we may receive and collect information about you provided to us by another user.

**Additional Information.** Providing additional information beyond what is required at registration is entirely optional, but enables you to better identify yourself and find products and Services offered by us. If you contact us by email through the Site, we may keep a record of your contact information and correspondence, and may use your email address, and any information that you provide to us in your message, to respond to you.

**Use of Contact Information.** We may use your contact information to market to you, and provide you with information about, our products and services, including but not limited to our Service. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such information or communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications.

**Use of Photographs and Other Profile Information.** We may display your photograph, video, name, address, postings, and any other profile information to other Site users (including unregistered visitors), whether pursuant to a search or randomly (including display on the front page of the Site) and on other websites operated by us. We may also share your photograph, video, name, address, postings, and any other profile information with third-parties who may display this information on websites unaffiliated with the Site.

**Log Data.** When you visit the Site, our servers may automatically record information that your browser sends (either automatically or upon request) whenever you visit a website ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information (without limitation) such as your IP address, browser type or the domain from which you are visiting, the web-pages you visit, the search terms you use, and any advertisements on which you click. For most users accessing the Internet from an Internet service provider the IP address will be different every time you log on. We may use Log Data to monitor the use of the Site and of our Service, and for the Site's technical administration. We do not associate your IP address with any other personally identifiable information to identify you personally, except in case of violation of the Terms of Service or pursuant to a subpoena or a court order.

**Information from other websites.** We may institute programs with advertising partners and other websites in which they share information with us:

    * **1.** We may ask advertisers to tell us how our users responded to the ads we showed them (and for comparison purposes, how other users who didn't see the ads acted on their site). This data sharing, commonly known as "conversion tracking," helps us measure our advertising effectiveness and improve the quality of the advertisements you see.
    * **2.** We may receive information about whether or not you've seen or interacted with certain ads on other sites in order to measure the effectiveness of those ads.

If in any of these cases we receive data that we do not already have, we will "anonymize" it within 180 days, meaning we will stop associating the information with any particular user. If we institute these programs, we will only use the information in the ways we explain within this Privacy Policy.

**Information from other users.** We may collect information about you from and pursuant to the request of other Site users.

  * ### Cookies

Like many websites, we also use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve the Site and our service. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard disk. We do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information. FINDANDTRY may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with the Site and our Service, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on the Site, and to improve the Site and our services. A session cookie enables certain features of the Site and our service and is deleted from your computer when you disconnect from or leave the Site. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.

  * ### Information Sharing and Disclosure

**Service Providers.** We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, including, without limitation, hosting and maintenance, customer relationship, database storage and management, and direct marketing campaigns. We will share your personally identifiable information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to binding contractual obligations requiring such third parties to maintain the privacy and security of your data.

**Affiliates.** We may share your personally identifiable information, posted content, User Data and all other content and messages provided by you with third-parties who offer their own services to users and direct user traffic to the Site.

**Business Transfers.** FINDANDTRY may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your personally identifiable information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if the new entity's planned processing of your information differs materially from that set forth in this Privacy Policy.

  * ### Security

FINDANDTRY is very concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information. We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access.

We will make any legally-required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored personal data to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

  * ### Links to Other Websites

Our Site contains links to other websites. The fact that we link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personally identifiable information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personally identifiable information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

  * ### Our Policy Towards Children

The Site and the Services are not directed to persons under 18. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child under 18 has provided us with personally identifiable information, he or she should contact us at privacy@findandtry.com. We do not knowingly collect or display personally identifiable information from children under 18. If we become aware that a child under 18 has provided us with personal identifiable information, we will delete such information from our files.
